<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Cases on Three Thirds</title>
    <link>https://threethirds.ai/cases/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Cases on Three Thirds</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://threethirds.ai/cases/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://threethirds.ai/cases/flexblow/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://threethirds.ai/cases/flexblow/</guid>
      <description>Real-time bottle blowing control system Client&amp;rsquo;s challenge FlexBlow is an SME specializing in PET bottle manufacturing and equipment. Their flagship product is a stretch blow molding machine that can be flexibly reconfigured to produce different shapes of bottles. However, the entire production process needs human supervision and continuous parameter adjustment in order to maintain bottle quality. We were contracted by Flexblow to design and implement an autonomous bottle quality control system.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://threethirds.ai/cases/girteka/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://threethirds.ai/cases/girteka/</guid>
      <description>Operational change impact measurement Client&amp;rsquo;s challenge Girteka is the largest full truck load transport company in Europe, with more than 8000 trucks in its fleet. In 2020, they started a digital transformation and were onboarding a vendor for load planning optimization. We were tasked with assessing company&amp;rsquo;s needs and providing an accurate measurement of the impact of this optimization.
Our solution  We delivered a suite of KPIs that were aligned with all the stakeholders, as well as an implementation of necessary computations, a dashboard for visualization, and a detailed documentation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://threethirds.ai/cases/rubedos/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://threethirds.ai/cases/rubedos/</guid>
      <description>Pallet detection and localization system Client&amp;rsquo;s challenge Rubedos is an SME specializing in mobile robotics. In 2021 they started developing an autonomous forklift platform, aiming to autonomously locate a pallet in a loading zone and transfer it to the target location. We were contracted by Rubedos to develop a pallet detection and localization stack that identifies pallets, their orientation and location from a stereo image and LIDAR inputs.
Our solution  Pallet detection system is based on an ensemble of off-the-shelf convolutional neural networks for object detection, adapted to the constraints of Rubedos&amp;rsquo; GPU-powered VIPER stereo camera.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://threethirds.ai/cases/strato/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://threethirds.ai/cases/strato/</guid>
      <description>Modular house planning  Client&amp;rsquo;s challenge strato.homes is an innovative startup that designs and builds modular houses from purchase to move-in in mere three months. A part of their vision is an AI planner that would create a floor-plan based on buyer&amp;rsquo;s choices and engineering restrictions imposed by their modular system. We were contracted by strato.homes to build a prototype of the AI planner.
Our solution Our solution consists of three main components:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://threethirds.ai/cases/turimeda/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://threethirds.ai/cases/turimeda/</guid>
      <description>EndoArt: Aortic aneurysm segmentation and monitoring system Client&amp;rsquo;s challenge Turimeda is an early stage MedTech startup that wants to measure and monitor internal organs without tedious manual labeling effort. Their first product focuses on abdominal aortic aneurysm – a life-threatening condition when aorta, the main blood vessel, expands and may rupture. Turimeda aims to develop a suite of tools that would help doctors track the development of condition over time based on regularly performed CT scans.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
